doubleviking.com 2018-05-25

# Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting this site operated by SK Intertainment, Inc (the “Site”). We are committed to protecting your privacy online and to providing you with the very best experience we can on the Site. In order to do so, we may gather certain personal information about you. Please read the following policy to understand how your personal information will be treated as you make full use of the Site. This policy may change from time to time so please check back periodically.

What information do we collect?

When you visit the Site, we collect some basic information that does not identify individual users. This includes which pages are visited, types of products purchased, and any feedback from our visitors. We then aggregate this information with other pieces of information to improve the Site and make your experience on the Site as valuable and efficient as possible.

In addition, we may ask you for personal information at times, including (but not limited to) when you enter promotions or contests, and when you respond to a survey.

What do we do with the information we collect?

We use the information that we collect to provide our services, to contact you regarding new offers, and for advertising purposes. We also use the information to contact customers to further discuss customer interest in our company, the services that we provide, and to send information regarding our company or partners, such as promotions and events. When we send you emails that include a link to the Site, that link may contain an alphanumeric identifier that allows us to identify the person to whom we sent the message so that we can personalize our content for that individual. If we ever send you emails concerning new products or services that you did not expressly request, we will provide you with an email address by which you may opt out of receiving such emails.

With whom do we share your information and for what purpose?

The information we collect may also be sold, licensed, transferred, rebranded, updated, appended and/or shared with individuals and companies engaged in the sales, marketing, advertising, and publishing industries for various products and services in which you may be interested. When one or more of our business partners co-sponsor a service, promotion and/or contest, we may share some or all of the information collected in connection with such service, promotion or contest with the co-sponsor(s).

We may also share aggregate user information in a non-personally identifiable manner with advertisers and other third parties in order to present to users more targeted advertising, products and services.

We may contract with third parties to conduct research and marketing on our behalf. Such third parties will be fully bound by an obligation of confidentiality and may not use any personally-identifiable information provided by us other than as expressly instructed by us and in strict compliance with the terms of this Privacy Policy.

We may, from time to time, supplement the information we collect from you with outside records (e.g., information we obtain from other companies, including wireless providers) to enhance our ability to serve you, to tailor our content to you, and to offer you opportunities to purchase products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. To fulfill your requests for products and services (e.g., provide you with content via your mobile phone), we may share the personally identifiable information you provide with your mobile phone service provider or their partner and subcontractor companies. Our privacy policy does not cover such entities’ use of information. To learn more about your provider's privacy practices, you should consult its privacy policy.

What information do other parties collect?

Some advertisers or websites that have links on the Site may collect personally identifiable information about you when you access or utilize those links. We do not control the collection or use of such information, and the practices of those advertisers and websites are not covered by this Privacy Policy.

What are cookies and how do we use them?

The Site may use cookies to speed navigation, keep track of items, and provide you with custom-tailored content. We also use cookies to remember information you gave us so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit the Site. By showing us how and when you use the Site, cookies also help us see which areas are popular and which are not. We also collect IP addresses for system administration and to report aggregate information to our sponsors and advertisers. Some advertisers or websites that have links on the Site may also use their own cookies.

Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you'd prefer, you can set yours to refuse cookies. You may not be able to access areas of the Site if you turn off the cookies option.

Cooperation with law enforcement

We fully cooperate with law enforcement agencies in identifying those who use the Site for illegal activities. We reserve the right to release information about users who we believe are in violation of applicable laws or regulations. We also reserve the right to report to law enforcement agencies any activities that we reasonably believe to be unlawful.

Users Located Outside of the United States

We make an effort to protect the personal information of all users of the Site. If you are unsure whether this privacy policy is in conflict with the rules applicable where you are located, you should not submit your personal information to the Site. IN ADDITION, IF YOU ARE LOCATED WITHIN THE EUROPEAN UNION, YOU SHOULD NOTE THAT YOUR INFORMATION WILL BE TRANSFERRED TO THE UNITED STATES, THE LAWS OF WHICH MAY BE DEEMED BY THE EUROPEAN UNION TO HAVE INADEQUATE DATA PROTECTION. Users of the Site located in countries outside of the United States who submit personal information do thereby consent to the transfer of that information to and/or storage of the information in the United States.

COPPA compliance

The Site is not directed to children under the age of 13. We have designed this privacy policy in order to comply with the Children's Online Privacy Protection Act ("COPPA"). We will never knowingly collect any personal information about children under the age of 13. If we obtain actual knowledge that we have collected personal information about a child under the age of 13, that information will be immediately deleted from our database. Because we do not collect such information, we have no such information to use or to disclose to third parties.

If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to us, he or she can contact us via e-mail or postal mail as listed below. We will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child under the age of 13. Please note that it is possible some of this information may remain archived in web logs and back-up archives after we delete the information from its active database.

We believe that parents should supervise their children’s online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from otherwise disclosing online their name, address and other personal information without parental permission.

California User Consumer Rights.

Under California Civil Code Sec. 1789.3, California resident users are entitled to know that they may file grievances and complaints with California Department of Consumer Affairs, 400 R Street, STE1080, Sacramento, CA 95814; or by phone at 916-445-1254 or 800-952-5210; or by email to dca@dca.ca.gov. For more information about protecting your privacy, you may wish to visit: http: //www.ftc.gov.

Under California Civil Code Sections 1798.83-1798.84, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice identifying the categories of personal customer information that we share with our affiliates and/or third parties for marketing purposes, and providing contact information for such affiliates and/or third parties. If you are a California resident and would like a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: SK Intertainment, Privacy Rights, 1625 North Damen Avenue, Floor 2, Chicago, Illinois 60647.

Business transitions

In the event we go through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of a portion of our assets, users' personal information will, in most instances, be part of the assets transferred.

Your consent

By using the Site, you consent to the collection and use of your information as described in this policy, and you signify your agreement to this Privacy Policy.

Changes to our Privacy Policy

From time to time, we may change our Privacy Policy. We will post those changes on this page so that our customers will always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we share the information with others. It is your responsibility to check this page periodically.

Any questions regarding our Privacy Policy should be directed to privacy@skintertainment.com.
